Your father's cancer cells
have spread to the nearby lymph nodes.
It's currently at stage three.
What does stage three mean?
Is it serious?
You could say it's very serious.
But there's good news.
It hasn't metastasized yet.
Then...
How much longer does he have?
Normally, one to five years.
But with active treatment,
many people can live with the tumor.
Doctor,
I'm begging you.
Whatever it takes,
please, you absolutely have to save my dad.
Right now, standard treatment is chemo and radiation.
We'll do four to six cycles first,
then evaluate the results
to see if additional treatments are needed.
The patient's willpower is very important.
You need to keep him happy and cheerful.
Hear that?
The doctor said there's still a chance.
You have to believe in Uncle Chen.
Dad!
You have to hold on!
Hold on!
Hurry! Dad!
Dad!
Hang in there, Dad!
We're almost there! Almost there!
Just hold on a little longer!
We're almost there!
Where's my dad?
Doctor.
Could I ask you something?
Have you seen a man,
about this tall,
wearing a blue sweater?
An old man with a cane?
No, I haven't.
Sorry,
the number you have dialed is not answering.
Please try again later.
Where's my dad?
I can't find him.
Where's Dad?
He's not answering.
Do you think Dad might've...
No.
Don't think like that.
Listen, you guys search over there.
I'll search over here.
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Thank you for watching my kid, sir.
Thank you. Thank you.
No problem.
Thanks.
Work hard.
Let's go home.
I used to tell you to smoke less.
Now you know.
I know.
You're back!
I made some chicken soup just for you today.
It's already on the table.
I specifically bought a free-range chicken.
It's super tender.
And I made Dad his favorite steamed pork ribs.
Here.
The last dish is ready too.
Dad.
You came back by yourself?
Where are Xiaofang and her brother?
They'll be right back.
Today, I
bought a nice bottle of liquor.
Since they aren't back yet,
let's have a drink together first.
Alright.
I'll go get it right now.
Here.
For you, Dad.
Sip it slowly.
Here.
Drinking on an empty stomach is bad for you.
You need some food to go with your drink.
Here, have your favorite steamed pork.
You rascal.
You sure know how to butter me up.
When I first met you,
in my heart,
I was actually worried.
My Xiaofang got herself a boyfriend
who looked
so completely unreliable.
Dad.
To be honest with you,
I really was a bit unreliable before.
But don't worry.
I'm not the same as I used to be.
These past two years,
seeing how you are with Xiaofang,
I've taken it all to heart.
Our Xiaofang,
she has a sharp tongue but a soft heart.
Since you're so tolerant and protective of her,
my heart
is finally at ease.
Actually, to be honest,
I've always felt
that I don't have much to offer.
But Xiaofang is different.
She is very responsible.
I just hope that in the future,
whenever she's carrying a burden on her own,
I can share some of it for her.
Come on.
Let me toast you.
Alright.
You guys are back!
Go get two glasses,
let's all have a drink together.
Smells great.
Yeah.
Dad,
the doctor said
you're not allowed to drink.
Not allowed to drink?
Dad was diagnosed with cancer.
What?
Dad...
It's okay.
I won't be kicking the bucket just yet.
Dad, where are you going?
See this?
November 16th.
The 8th day of the 10th lunar month.
Auspicious for weddings.
A very lucky day.
A match made in heaven.
This is the perfect day.
You two should have your wedding then!
You got it, Dad.
Why are you guys just standing there?
Let's eat!
Smells so good.
Your cooking skills are getting better and better.
Thanks, Dad.
Zhou Fang,
I'll have a drink with you.
Okay.
Here.
Dad.
A toast to you.
Alright.
Good, good.
This is just wonderful.
You scared the hell out of me.
What are you blowing up all these balloons for?
Did you take a group order?
What group order?
You really think everything I do is for money.
That I'm just greedy.
I'm going to surprise them.
Then blow them up at the venue.
You blew up so many, how will you get them there?
You're worrying over nothing.
See this?
I took all these balloons
and strung them all together.
Besides,
I've got my convertible, don't I?
Firing a salute to welcome the guests.
It's a good omen.
Hurry up, wash your face and brush your teeth.
You look like a maniac.
I was just about to.
Geez.
They really are hard to carry.
My boss,
you're finally getting married today.
You have to be happy forever.
I will.
One, two, three.
It worked!
Great job, Yangyang.
Later, when the bride comes out,
you pop it just like this, okay?
Okay.
Good.
Were you scared, Yangyang?
No.
I wanna do it again.
You wanna do another one?
Alright, one more.
Uncle Daren.
You look really sharp today.
On such an important day,
of course I do.
How do I look?
Button your top button.
Alright, alright.
Take a picture of me.
Sure.
Ready.
One, two, three.
Yueru...
When you left, you told me
to raise the kids well
and keep them happy.
When they grew up,
to see them settle down.
I promised you I would.
Today,
Xiaofang
got married.
I've vetted this young man.
He's incredibly good to Xiaofang.
So you can rest easy.
I never expected
time to pass so quickly.
That tiny little baby from back then
has grown into a young woman.
I just didn't expect
that in the blink of an eye,
we'd be the ones listening to them.
Today
is truly a great day.
I chose it for them.
An auspicious day.
A match made in heaven.
It's a shame
you won't get to see it.
Who's crying?
These are tears of joy.
Let's go.
Let's go take a look.
It's so lively.
Hop on, then.
Let me scan you.
Here, here.
All three of you wear glasses.
You three should add each other on WeChat.
How old are you?
Me?
Sister Lan.
You're definitely not married.
Sister Lan!
Hurry up.
Yangyang is calling you.
Coming, coming.
You... you three go have a chat.
Go on, go have a drink.
Go grab a drink over there.
Yangyang's been calling you for ages.
Sweetie, I didn't hear you just now.
Godmom was busy.
I found a potential client, you know?
Oh, give it a rest.
Don't tell me you monopolized all matchmaking in town.
You have no idea.
My sense of smell is very sharp right now.
As soon as I take a sniff,
I immediately know who's single.
Single people always...
...give off a faint scent of absolute loneliness.
Then tell me, who's single here?
You, of course.
And you.
I think there's something going on between you two.
What are you laughing at?
Look at how happy she is.
We won't hide it anymore.
Show it to them.
Blind them with it.
Show what?
Oh my god.
A marriage certificate!
Wang Daren!
Wang Daren, come here and give me a hug right now!
Coming, coming!
Wang Daren, I can't take this anymore.
Give me a hug, quick!
Yes, yes, yes. Let's hug, let's hug.
Dating without the goal of marriage...
...is just messing around, isn't it?
Then your wedding...
...must be hosted by Xidongdong!
Bottoms up!
Great!
Leave it to Xidongdong.
Come on, come on.
Then you have to give us a discount.
A discount!
You two...
...should do a cross-arm toast!
No way!
Hurry up!
I really want to see it!
This PDA you're feeding me...
...is absolutely delicious!
Mr. Zhou.
The ceremony is about to start.
You need to get ready to go on stage.
Dad.
I... I thought you weren't coming.
It's my son's big day.
How could I not come?
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong to upset you before.
The one who should be sorry...
...is me.
For so many years,
because I was busy,
I missed so much of your growing up.
Instead, I always demanded
that you achieve so-called success.
Along the way,
you stumbled and struggled.
But I also saw your persistence,
and how hard it was.
You can support yourself now.
Xiaofang
deserves half the credit for that, I guess.
But to be honest, Dad,
I don't even know
if I'm ready or not.
All I know is
I really want to marry Xiaofang.
I can tell.
Xiaofang really wants what's best for you.
After you get married,
you'll definitely become
better versions of yourselves.
This money...
you can't give it back this time.
As your father,
this is my blessing to you.
Well, my dad's blessing...
I definitely have to accept.
Thanks, Dad.
Silly boy.
You've grown up.
Today is your big day.
You should be happy.
Your beautiful bride
is still waiting for you.
Go on.
Let's go.
Your Aunt Juan did this for me.
Doesn't it make me look
ten years younger?
My dad is the most handsome!
Xiaofang,
Dad
can only walk you this far today.
For the days ahead,
you'll have to walk on your own.
But you must remember,
Dad
will always have your back.
I'll always support you.
And now,
please welcome our most beautiful bride
to make her entrance!
Go on.
Go and bravely pursue
your own happiness.
Now,
will the bride and groom please exchange rings.
Finally, the moment we've all been waiting for!
Now, it's time for the bride
to toss her bouquet!
Go on, go! Stand in the middle!
Hurry, hurry! Come on, everyone!
Come on, come on!
One, two, three!
Okay, for real this time!
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss!
What's wrong with you, kid?
You're such a slowpoke!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I really can't stand you!
Hurry up!
Yiran!
I actually have a lot I want to tell you,
but every time I try to say it,
I chicken out.
And then I feel the timing isn't right.
Look at the two of us.
Since we graduated high school,
we've been like two parallel lines.
One went to Beijing,
and the other to Shanghai.
I thought
our paths would never cross again.
But I didn't expect
fate to come full circle,
and bring us both back to our hometown.
From Pet Paradise's collapse and the debts
to working together at Xiaoxitian,
we've really been through so much.
Yeah, so much.
Do you remember Grandma Xiufang?
At that time, you told me
what it means to be an actor.
The art of acting lies in
interpreting another person's life.
For an actor,
isn't that the most joyful and meaningful thing?
Here.
Tastes good?
It's good.
It gave me the courage in that moment
to use Xizi's identity
and accompany Grandma Xiufang on her final journey.
At that time,
I thought on the surface, you fought the whole world,
tougher than rock.
But in my eyes,
your heart is softer than anyone's.
You know better than anyone
how to live.
The word "regret,"
in our line of work,
we know how heavy it is.
Yeah, regret.
Regret.
I, I, I... Why am I talking about this?
I... I actually wanted to say...
What... what did I want to say?
I... I wanted to say...
What I actually wanted to say is...
when... when I first saw you,
I was really happy.
Especially when you were... at the police station.
And do you remember being in Wu Yuanfeng's office?
You were slamming books all over the place.
You scared that boss so much
he yelled to kick that little girl out immediately.
I felt like you melted everyone's hearts back then.
Including mine.
You melted mine, too.
Li Yiran.
I like you.
Will you be with me?
Chen Baixi.
You're really rambling today.
Dad.
I bought you a gift.
That's an improvement!
Did you find anything?
I know where Grandma Sun's last letter is.
Let's go.
So soon?
We're leaving, Uncle Chen.
We're leaving, Dad.
Where are you going?
We'll wait for you for dinner!
Starting today,
I, Chen Xiaofang, am officially shedding the slacker title!
I'm going to work with Xiaofang
to take Xidongdong and Xiaoxitian
out of Lecang
and onto the global stage!
Yeah!
Clap louder!
What's the matter?
So it seems that from now on, Xidongdong
is going to rely entirely on me.
Absolutely!
Sister Lan is our anchor!
What is this?
Thousand-year-old ancient tree tea.
And you only poured one cup?
How thoughtless.
Come on.
To our two new students,
here's to your academic success!
Cheers!
Thanks, Auntie Lan.
Why are you drinking all by yourself?
What about me?
You're working at Uncle Daren's tonight.
Be quick on your feet,
and mind your manners.
Got it?
Got it, Mom.
Go on.
Yangyang is the best!
Boss!
Are our skewers ready yet?
These are yours.
I'll bring them right over.
Hurry up.
Go, quick.
Alright, alright.
Coming right up!
Okay, thanks.
No problem.
Bring us a bottle of beer!
Sure, sure, sure.
Do you have any? Yes.
Are my skewers ready yet?
The ones for that table.
Right away, right away!
Chives.
Thanks.
Yangyang.
May your journey to paradise
be free from earthly suffering.
Sister Liu.
Rest in peace.
Want another drink?
No, I'm good.
You two...
should just get back to your own things.
Tell your sister
she doesn't need to come tonight.
We aren't comfortable leaving you alone.
I'll stay and keep you company.
Xiaofang
is married now.
Are they doing alright?
Yesterday at the shop,
Xiaofang was practically walking on air.
She said someone drives her to and from work now.
And gets her a coat when it's cold.
Really showing off their love.
Your mother and I,
back in the day,
when we first got married,
used to fight all the time.
Sometimes,
if the food was too salty or bland,
we'd get into a big argument.
I thought you two
never even had a single fight.
When living as a married couple,
you're bound to bump heads.
It's just that,
after arguing so much,
we finally figured out
what should be said,
and what shouldn't.
Xiaofang has her own family now.
While I'm still around,
you and Yiran need to hurry up.
You must be good to Yiran.
And treat your mother-in-law well.
Keep that in mind.
You and your sister,
don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
Even if
the day actually comes
when I pass away,
just think of it as
me going to see your mom.
Your mom
was always timid.
She's been over there
for so many years now.
It's about time I go
and keep her company.
You're a grown man. What are you crying for?
It's not like I'm passing on right away.
Someday,
our family
will see each other again.
Your mom and I
are just heading to the other side
to get our home
set up first.
How old was I here?
About a year old?
One month.
At one, you'd be this tall.
You were already learning to walk.
I don't remember.
Look how silly you look.
Whenever I said "take a picture,"
you'd have a piece of candy in your mouth,
and strike a pose right away.
Do you remember this photo?
This... I remember this.
You made me pose like this.
You said supermodels all posed like this.
Either a headache,
or a stomachache,
or a backache.
This is the backache.
This is the stomachache.
This... this is the headache.
You remember this one, right?
Look.
You got your ears pierced at ten.
Just to look pretty.
You were so tough.
You didn't cry at all.
It actually hurt a lot.
Of course it hurt.
Are you nervous?
Nervous about what?
Aren't you going to Chen Baixi's house for dinner tomorrow?
It's just...
it's just a casual dinner.
Let's stop looking.
A family heirloom.
Know what this is?
What is it?
This is from the day I got married.
The calendar page your grandma tore off.
And this.
This bracelet is so pretty.
It must be expensive.
No matter how expensive,
I could never sell it.
Even during the hardest times,
I still kept it.
Your grandma left this to me.
Grandma gave it to you. I can't take it.
Grandma left it to me,
which means it's meant for you. Put it on.
You have to remember,
as long as Mom is here, you have a home.
No matter what happens in the future,
Mom will always have your back.
I know, I know.
Comrade Wu Huilan.
Like hell you know.
Silly girl.
Many times, I forget
that before Mom became a mother,
she was also a daughter.
Grandma gave all her love to Wu Huilan,
and Wu Huilan
gave all her love
to me.
Mom
I can't bear to let you go.
So silly.
What the hell are you crying for?
What's wrong with you?
You're not coming back?
Of course I'll be back.
You're...
Happy New Year!
I was just about to say,
that scarf looks really pretty on you.
Of course.
It depends on who bought it.
Why are your palms so sweaty?
Who wouldn't be nervous meeting their mother-in-law?
What are you nervous about?
Don't you see her all the time?
That was before.
I used to just call her Auntie Lan.
It's different now.
Then you'd better be on your best behavior later.
Maybe as a reward for calling her "Mom",
Wu Huilan will give you a big red envelope.
Whatever the amount, I'll hand it all over to you.
You really are an acting major.
Your acting is totally superficial.
But it still couldn't escape your sharp eyes.
Happy New Year!
Li Yiran
What are you looking at?
An acquaintance.
Let's go. Everyone's waiting for New Year's Eve dinner.
Let's go.
Alright, alright.
The red envelopes are here.
Okay, thanks.
This red envelope is yours.
Thanks, Dad. Thanks, Dad.
Coming, coming.
Time for dumplings.
Coming.
Dumplings are here.
Thanks for your hard work, young Boss Zhou.
May you have abundance every year.
My dear in-law,
this hotpot base you made
is getting better and better.
You bet it is.
It's my specialty.
You should eat more.
Okay.
We're late.
Happy New Year!
We've been looking forward to this,
and you're finally here.
Come, come.
Quick, sit down.
Okay.
You silly boy.
Where are the manners I taught you?
What?
Mom.
That was too quiet.
Nobody heard that, right?
Didn't hear it.
Louder.
Mom!
That's better, that's better.
You, hurry up.
Dad.
Great, great.
I've had the red envelope ready for a while.
Thanks, Dad.
Sister Lan, hurry and give him the red envelope.
This is for you. We brought it for you.
Thanks, Dad.
Come on, come on.
Give it to me. I'll help you hold it.
Son-in-law.
I can call you my son-in-law now, right?
Of course.
Here, a red envelope from Mom.
From now on, we're family.
You have to treat Yiran well.
Otherwise, Mom will...
Mom.
Don't worry.
I will treat her well for the rest of my life.
I won't let her suffer the slightest wrong.
That's more like it.
I believe you.
Sit.
Quick, quick.
Everyone is here.
Let's have a drink together.
Come, come.
Cheers.
Happy New Year!
Come on, let's eat.
Here.
Dad, have some crispy pork.
Yangyang.
Let's add some meatballs.
The meat ones, right?
For a happy reunion.
Let me, let me.
I'll put the meatballs in.
It's the New Year.
Let's liven things up a bit.
You two.
Give each other a kiss.
Right now?
Kiss! Kiss!
What's the big deal? Come on.
One more!
Did you even kiss on the lips?
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss!
You guys are making me blush.
Come, Mom wants a kiss too.
That's enough, right?
Enough, enough.
Amin.
You're way too shy.
Exactly.
Juan, you make the first move.
Let's kiss Yangyang together.
Come on.
That works, that works.
In-law!
You're so pitiful.
No one's giving you a kiss.
Let's...
Let's all give Dad a kiss together.
Happy New Year, Dad!
Happy New Year!
You all gave him a kiss!
Wang Daren, you're on your own.
I'll blow you a kiss.
In-law,
at this table,
you must be the oldest here.
So you should start us off.
Say a blessing.
Everyone says one.
We'll go in a circle.
Sound good?
Yes, yes, yes!
Sounds good! Sounds good!
Come on, here we go.
Alright, alright, alright.
Then I'll toast with tea.
Wishing all our old pals
good health
and a great appetite!
Hear, hear!
And to the young folks,
stay forever young!
Good, good, good!
Nice!
My turn!
I'll say something practical.
Wishing everyone bulging wallets!
Make a fortune this New Year!
That's great.
Alright.
Then I'll say something impractical.
Wishing everyone
abundant blessings
and endless good luck!
Come on, let's drink to that.
Bottoms up.
A lovers' toast!
Alright!
You might pop out a baby later!
For our family,
Lijuan will represent us.
Don't make me represent us.
You go first.
Come on, stand up, stand up.
Yangyang, stand up. Come on.
I'll say it. Here I go.
Wishing everyone, uh...
A booming life full of joy,
and growing wealth year by year!
Nice!
So cultured! Very poetic!
Then I wish everyone
gets more beautiful every year!
Great!
What about Yangyang? What about Yangyang?
Happy New Year!
Speaking a foreign language now!
Come on.
Daren, your turn to speak.
Alright, alright.
Uncle Daren.
You guys are done.
I have to say mine now.
Wishing everyone's life is like this hotpot,
booming and bustling!
Great!
Good, good, good!
Then
I'll drink to that with you.
Sounds good!
Sounds good! Sounds good!
Then I wish everyone
that everything goes your way.
May your wishes come true.
I wish everyone in the new year
a life like fireworks,
gorgeous and colorful!
Nice!
Thank you, sister-in-law.
You're welcome, sis.
New year, new vibes.
May our Chunguang Alley
become happier and happier.
May life be as bright as spring every day!
Hear, hear!
Happy New Year!
So beautiful.
Returning to my hometown from Shanghai,
I thought it would just be a brief stay,
but it turned out to be a long and gentle pause.
I drew closer to death,
No!
and drew closer to life once again.
Thank you. Thank you.
Those departing figures, one after another, made me realize
that saying goodbye is never the end.
The love hidden in the little things of life
Grandma will make it for you again tomorrow.
Okay, okay.
quietly becomes a footnote to our lives.
Just take a sip.
These seemingly trivial yet real daily moments
remind us that
life is a constant loss.
Why is it you?
Close your eyes, quick.
But it's also a constant gain.
Every parting is a promised reunion.
Everything we lose
will echo back in another form.
Dad is the best in the world.
Those hurdles we thought we couldn't cross,
and wounds we thought would never heal,
looking back,
have all become scenery left behind.
Dad.
Whoever of you
takes on this funeral today,
I'll disown you!
Wu Huilan!
Those seemingly unbreakable barriers,
just like winter snow,
will eventually melt away.
From now on,
let's all just be ourselves.
For the rest of our lives,
we will still face pain,
parting, and death.
Some people are forever stuck in yesterday,
while we, today,
still have to run forward
and welcome every sunrise.
Even if reality is cruel,
we must strive to grow upward.
I'm not afraid of you!
You work so hard studying.
Don't touch me!
Those seemingly futile efforts
will eventually, at some corner,
turn into unexpected surprises.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Those we thought we'd never see again
are guarding you in another way,
turning into starlight to light the way ahead,
guiding us to the shores of happiness.
And we will all be there,
making peace with all our obsessions and regrets,
heading toward a new life,
in an endless cycle of life.
Let's head back.
You are...
Let's take a photo!
Boss Zhou,
take a group photo for us.
Come on!
Everyone look there!
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
Uncle Li.
I've come to see you.
Mom, who's this?
We came last year, too.
He saved Mom's life.
Yiran!
Without him,
Liangliang wouldn't be here.
Thank you for saving my mom.
I carved these by hand. They're all for you.
Let's go.
Unbelievable.
Forcing me to dress like this.
Dad would jump out of his grave if he saw this.
Good if he does.
Let him see
how pretty we both look,
how glamorous we're dressed,
and how great our lives are.
Great my ass.